Over a century ago, beings that
prey on humans suddenly appeared.
Their absolutely overwhelming strength
quickly pushed humanity to
the brink of extinction.
The surviving humans constructed
three walls: Maria, Rose, and Sina,
which brought them a century of peace.
However...
In the year 845, the Colossal Titan
and the Armored Titan suddenly appeared
and destroyed one of humanity's
walls-- and everyday life with it.
Humanity abandoned Wall Maria,
lost twenty percent of its population
and one-third of its territory,
and was forced to
retreat behind Wall Rose.
In the year 850, the Colossal
Titan demolished another wall
and allowed the Titans inside once again.
Eren!
Hurry!
The entire populace was
evacuated two hours later.
Not a single person was eaten by a Titan...
...except for the soldiers who fended
them off and died in the line of duty.
Eren.
As long as I have you,
I can do anything.
Unknown are the names
of the flowers that have been trampled
Birds have fallen to the earth
and long for the wind
Prayers won't solve anything
Only the will to fight
can change the here and now!
O pigs who laugh at the resolve
to walk over corpses to move forward
Livestock complacency? False prosperity?
Give us the freedom of dying,
starving wolves!
The humiliation of being caged
is what triggers us to fight back
We hunters slaughter prey
beyond the castle walls,
consumed with surging bloodlust,
as our crimson bows and arrows
pierce scarlet holes into the twilight
"Small Blade"
"The Struggle for Trost, Part 3"
Please wait, Captain!
Should the Titans attack,
we supply soldiers won't be able
to hold this position on our own!
Please, Sir! You have to stay here!
Step aside.
I must reorganize the
reinforcements now.
Behind the safety of
the inner gate, you mean?
What the hell are you trying to say?
I'll have you know I'm following regulations!
Obeying established
regulations is a soldier's duty!
B-But, Sir!
If we lose this position...!
Enough of your talk!
Open your mouth again
and I'll be forced to punish
you for treason where you stand!
Why isn't anyone going over the wall?
I'm sure they heard the
bell signaling us to withdraw...
It's all over...
We're done for...
There!
What good is that going to do?
C'mon, Jean! What are we gonna do?!
Ain't anything we can do...
They finally gave the order to withdraw,
but we don't have enough
gas to scale the wall...
We're all gonna die now...
All 'cause of those cowards...
You mean the supply soldiers?!
What's happened to them?!
Were they wiped out?!
Apparently they lost the will to fight.
I can understand the feeling,
but abandoning
their duty to supply us
so they can barricade
themselves inside Headquarters?
And sure enough,
Titans have swarmed the place,
meaning we can't even
get gas for ourselves.
In that case, it's sink or swim!
We'll just have to
take out the Titans there!
Hanging around here's no different!
The Titans will just gather here too!
We'll only use up what little gas we
have left if we keep running aimlessly!
Once we lose our mobility,
we're really done for!
You're actually using
your head for once, Conny.
But do you really think we
have the manpower to pull that off?
Most of the veteran members of
the vanguard have been wiped out.
We're just cadets;
who can possibly take charge of
a suicide mission like that?
Even if someone could,
it's not like we'd stand a chance
against the Titans anyway.
And the supply room's probably got
some that are three or four meters high.
There's no way we could
get anything done in there.
It's hopeless?
What a dull life this was.
If I'd known this would happen,
I would've said something sooner.
Come on, guys! Let's do it!
Get up!
If we all work together,
we're sure to succeed!
I'll take the lead!
Armin! Let's go--!
Reiner.
What now?
Not yet. We have to let them gather first.
It's no use...
However you look at it,
we're not getting out of this city.
We're all dead.
I mean, I'm ready
to die and everything...
It's just... what am I dying for?
Mikasa!
Weren't you with the rearguard?!
Annie!
I understand the gist of the situation.
So I'm sorry for letting
my personal matters interfere...
...but have you seen Eren's squad?
I haven't, but some squads did
make it over the wall...
Actually, we did find Armin over there.
Armin!
Mikasa...
No! I can't bring myself to face her!
All I did was survive for
no good reason...
If I'd known this would happen...
...I would rather have
died with him then instead!
Armin.
You're not hurt, are you?
Are you all right?
Where's Eren?
Armin?
We...
The cadets of Squad 34...
Thomas Wagner...
Nack Tierce...
Milieus Zeremski...
Mina Carolina...
Eren Jaeger...
These five members...
...fulfilled their duties...
...and died valiantly
on the field of battle!
You can't be serious...
So Squad 34 is basically gone...
The same thing'll happen to
us if we try to take the Titans on...
I'm sorry, Mikasa...
It should've been me, not Eren...
I...
...wasn't able to do anything...!
I'm sorry...
Armin.
Calm down.
Now isn't the time to be emotional.
Now get up.
Marco.
If we eliminate the Titans
swarming around HQ,
we can replenish our gas
supplies and get over the wall.
Correct?
Well, yeah...
But even with your help,
there's just too many...
I can handle them.
Huh?!
I'm strong.
Stronger than all of you.
I'm very strong.
As such, I am capable of
annihilating the Titans there!
Even if I have to go it alone.
As for all of you,
you're not only unskilled,
you're also cowards and wimps.
You're a real disappointment.
You can just stay here
and twiddle your thumbs.
Twiddle and watch.
Whoa, Mikasa!
What's gotten into you?!
You're seriously gonna take
on all those Titans by yourself?!
There's no way you can beat them!
If I can't, then I'll die.
It's that simple.
But...
If I win, I'll live.
And the only way to win is to fight!
Hey!
Your way with words
is the real disappointment.
You actually considered
that motivational...
I blame you for this, Eren...!
Hey! Since when were we taught
to let our comrades fight alone?!
Or do you guys want
to end up as actual cowards?!
Never thought I'd hear him say that.
Come on, you cowards,
weaklings, and morons!
Those guys...
Damn it...
All right, let's do it!
Hurry!
Follow Mikasa!
Fight as little as possible!
Get to HQ before you run out of gas!
Man, Mikasa's incredible...
How can she move so fast?!
No! She's using up too much gas!
She's going to run out right away!
Regardless of our skill,
once we lose our mobility
we're completely helpless!
She's not her usual,
composed self at all!
She's trying to distract
herself from her anguish!
It's only a matter of time until she...!
Mikasa!
Damn!
Jean!
You take the lead!
I'll help Armin!
--No, I will too!
--Don't be stupid!
There are still Titans everywhere!
Your skills are needed!
Again...
It's this again...
I've lost my family again...
Do I have to revisit this pain...
...and start all over from here again?
It's no use. We can't
even get near Headquarters.
Unless we're prepared to die...
Crap! He's out of gas!
Stay back!
--Tom! I'll save you!
--No!
It's too late!
Stop!
Why couldn't I stop them...?
Why didn't I stop them?
If I'd made them stop,
this wouldn't have happened...
Am I really cut out for this?
Am I really fit to have
a position of responsibility?!
No!
This world is cruel.
And...
...very beautiful.
It's been a nice life.
Huh?
Why?
I was sure I'd given up...
Why... am I standing up?
Why... am I struggling?
What for?
After all...
There's no point
in living anymore...
So what's driving me?
Fight!
Fight! Fight!
Eren...
Fight!
You have to fight!
I'm sorry, Eren...
I won't give up anymore...
I'll never give up again...
If I die...
...I'll lose my memories of
you too, on top of everything else.
So...
...I'll do whatever it takes to win!
Whatever it takes to live!
What just happened?!
A Titan...
...is killing...
...another Titan...
Please, Mikasa!
Be all right!
Mikasa!
Mikasa! Are you all right?!
--You two okay?!
--Yeah!
We gotta get out of here!
Crap! Two 15-meter ones!
No, that Titan is...
Huh?!
I-It finished it off?!
It was actually aware of
its weak spot?!
We gotta get out of here!
Before it comes this way!
No, it's not reacting to us.
Any other one
would attack us for sure...
It seemed to grasp the concept
of hand-to-hand combat too.
Just what is it...?
All we can do is chalk it
up as an Abnormal!
We barely know
anything about 'em, after all.
Now let's just hurry to HQ!
Wait! Mikasa's completely out of gas!
Huh?!
Whoa, are you serious?!
Now what are we gonna do?!
We need you!
The answer's obvious!
I don't have much left...
...but hurry and
switch yours with mine!
Armin!
This is our only option!
It'll amount to nothing if I keep it.
Just...
Use it carefully this time.
Everyone's lives are riding on it.
I took charge without any sense
of responsibility for their lives...
For a short time, I had
even thrown away my own life...
All for my own personal reasons.
I'm...
There!
Your mobility gear still works,
and I've given you all my blades.
All I ask is that you
leave me with this one...
I'd rather not get
eaten alive, if I can help it.
N-No way...
Armin.
I'm not leaving you here.
Back there...
...I was completely confused.
I'd never heard of a
Titan killing another Titan before.
But I also felt a
faint glimmer of elation.
Because what I saw...
...looked like the manifestation
of humankind's anger.
Your dreams are where your heart is
They're more fragile than life itself
Over and over you cast them aside,
only to find more
Now, rest in peace
Pounding impulses defile the things we wish for
and the more we forget
the more we remember again
In this beautiful, cruel world
all I can do is ask why we're still alive
Oh, with our strength--and our weakness--
what are we going to protect if there's no sense
to anything anymore?
A Titan that kills other Titans.
The sight of it leaves the 104th Cadet
Corps Class awestruck and breathless.
What ultimately appears
before them, though, is...